Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
Young Master Yamato!
Where are you going?!
The armory lies at the deepest level
of the underground!
Can I reach it in time?
Momonosuke-kun!
You must slow the island's advance,
even if only slightly!
Momonosuke-kun!
'Tis trying, but I shall persevere!
Show your guts!
Momonosuke, you can do this!
You can still do more!
You must create more
Flame Clouds...
Stronger Flame Clouds,
mighty enough to rival Kaido's!
More and more!
I shall not allow Onigashima
to reach the Flower Capital!
Trafalgar...
Your ability's awakened, hasn't it?
I'm not used to it yet...
I'd use it if it meant the difference between life and death,
but it drains the hell outta my stamina...
It could end up being
a critical misstep in a fight.
Same here.
But we ain't getting
anywhere like this!
Better be ready to back me up
with your ace in the hole!
I know, Kaido!
About the great armory
at the lowest level of the castle!
I know what's there!
The weapons I ordered made,
along with a massive stockpile of ammunition!
There's going to be a
huge, huge, huge explosion!
Set it alight, Kanjuro!
Blow everything to smithereens!
To the abyss, to the abyss...
And we shall host the greatest finale
at the Kurozumi Clan's graveyard!
It is over!
It all ends here!
I tire of dealing with utter fools!
Come to me at once, Fukurokuju!
Flower Shuriken!
Mere trifle!
Earlobe Crackers!
I shall lay waste to our lord's enemies!
Nin!
Ninja think of nothing
but their duty!
Let us escape from here!
Escape, I say!
Before Onigashima is
engulfed in flames and explodes!
A war between pirates
is none of our business!
Naughty brats like you
need to be taught a harsh lesson!
Sovereignty!
I got one of you, didn't I...
Kid!
Those two are keeping Big Mom at bay?
How incredible!
I'll have your head!
Better be ready to back me up
with your ace in the hole!
K-Room:
Anesthesia!
I'm gonna make this
real painful for you!
And I'm gonna give ya
the worst pain of your life!
The penetration itself is harmless...
But K-Room...
...generates an internal shockwave!
Shock Wille!
Mama! You're bleeding!
How dare you,
you damn runt!
I'll make you more attractive!
Assign!
Huh? I'm stuck to Mama!
What the hell is this?!
Did you just turn me into a magnet?!
More, more...!
There's more where that came from!
The towers' steel beams are gonna...
...collapse!
Oh, crap!
Uh?!
Release it, Trafalgar!
Don't give me orders!
Punk Clash!
She was crushed
by those steel beams!
She's gotta be dead...
Not even Big Mom can...!
There's my ace in the hole...
How d'ya like that,
hag from hell?!
So the awakened
Magnet-Magnet Fruit power...
...lets you turn anything
into a magnet, huh.
How long does it last?
Why the hell should I show you
what's in my hand?
She's back on her feeeet!
Life...
...or...
...oshiruko!
Oh, no!
That's her Soul Pocus!
"Life or oshiruko"?!
We've got some oshiruko,
don't we?!
Nope, we dumped it all...
If we don't got the soup,
she's gonna steal our lifespans!
Get up, all of you!
I give you life!
I'm gonna use
a year's worth of my lifespan...
There's no other way
to make myself stronger.
She's getting bigger...
Well, the bigger she is,
the better for us...
Gimme a break...
Kick her ass or dice it,
it's gonna be a pain either way...
How is this possible?!
She's gigantified!
That, and the castle's ablaze!
It doesn't get more dangerous than this!
Aye...
The Performance Floor's...
...a living hell!
haven't felt this much pain...
...in decades...!
I'm impressed,
Trafalgar Law...
...and "Captain" Kid!
Straw Hat Luffy, as well...
I'm sure of it now,
you've all come for my throne!
Can't believe I gotta
put down this monster...
...just so I can
learn more about history!
Give it all ya got,
don't hold anything back!
We're yankin' her off that throne,
even if it kills us!
Then claim it, if you can!
Prove you're worthy of
being an Emperor of the Sea!
Ahead of me lies
nothing but soldiers!
I must circumvent them
by way of the sacred cave!
Whoa, wait a sec!
You lost it or something?!
You don't got any reason to be slicing me!
Arguing is pointless!
Screw you, then!
Scratch!
Boom!
I already figured out
how your attacks work!
They're not going to work on me.
You're bluffing!
Your lines of attack...
...are hard to see,
but they are there!
Activation requires the target's hearing.
And the scope is your eyes!
Don't give it all away!
Won't make any difference anyway!
You're screwed,
'cause I've got three of the Numbers here!
Doesn't matter!
To fulfill my duty to Straw Hat,
I need to put you down!
Huh?
Drake! Apoo!
What is one of the Flying Six
and an informant doing here?
I oughta be asking you that, Young Master!
What're you doing here?
I thought you were
fighting against Kaido...
I need to reach the armory!
Yamato...
Yamato!
He's one of Kaido's enemies!
Drake, that idiot...
He's useless anyway!
How about we swap, then?
Drake, let me...
Wait a sec, wait a sec,
Young Master Yamato!
Have I got some good news for you!
Whatever it is,
I do not have time for!
I have severed ties with Kaido!
Do not think of me as your ally!
Seriously?!
Then we really gotta talk!
At any rate, I haven't the time
to chat with you lot!
Make way, Animal Kingdom Pirates!
You will not bar my path!
Wait, Yamato! I...
If you will not move...
I shall make you!
Wait, dammit!
Do not even think you can stop me!
Make way at once!
I've broken off from
the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
I don't have anything
to do with Kaido, either!
Eh?! Really, now?!
Apologies, Drake...
But I must hurry!
Off I go...
Until then!
Onigashima and
the Flower Capital are in danger!
Hey!
Dammit! Every last one of 'em...
None of 'em are followin' my beat!
I gotta Yamato on my side somehow!
Where are you going, Fuga?!
V
What the...?!
Eh?!
Fuga!
See you later!
Hey, Fuga....
Whaaaa?!
Where ya going, Fuga?!
Stop!
What the hell is going on?!
Hey!
Let's stop them!
Follow me, guys!
I won't let you get away,
Young Master Yamato!
I won't let you get away, Apoo!
Run, Baron Corpse!
Why, though?
Protect Nico Robin!
We'd rather you leave them to us.
Minks!
Go, Baron Corpse!
Robin-san!
Let's be off!
Brook!
We shan't let their
sacrifice be in vain!
For them to defeat
the Minks so handily...
Who are they, truly?
They're a Cipher Pol unit, CP-0.
They were at Dress Rosa...
Cipher PolThe intelligence bureau
working directly for the Government, right?!
Why are they here
on Onigashima, though?
I don't know...
All I know is, the situation
can't possibly get any worse.
Eh?
Of all the elements of CP-0,
the top-ranking unit in Cipher Pol,
the masked agents are exceptions
among the exceptional.
If you'll allow me, Robin-san...
Up and away!
What should I do?
Chuji!
Where did you go, Chuji?
E-Excuse me! I...
Please, you must help me!
Judge once said...
I am just a geisha,
brought in from the Flower Capital!
With the power of science...
Shut up...
he'd create a warrior
with an unfeeling heart of ice!
Shut up!
I'm begging you! Please let me go!
That Germa blood you've got in ya has gotta
be goin' crazy right now, right?!
Shut up! I'm...
...human, dammit!
You okay, m'lady?
Stay away from me!
Stay away...!
Help me!
O-Some, what happened?!
You're bleeding!
Who would do such a thing?!
Are you okay? Let me help!
How could you do this
to such a young girl?!
Wait, please!
There's been a misunderstanding!
Not another word!
You're one of
Wano's soldiers, are you not?
That's right...
How dare you do this to your own?!
I didn't, though!
Please, just listen to me!
I'm pretty sure I...
I didn't do anything...
Didn't do anything...
...to her...
I think...
Enough of your lies!
O-Some was running from you!
Leave here at once!
This is our hiding place!
You've some nerve, raising your hand
against a harmless woman!
That can't be true! I...
You brute!
To hell with cowards!
Begone already!
I...
That's impossible....!
I'd never harm a lady!
Hey!
Germa!
Where've you been?
I thought the Pleasure Hall was closed!
No! That's the last thing I'd do!
How could I lay a hand on...
Knocking a woman
unconscious like that...!
Everything about all of you
goes against what I stand for!
Am I gonna end up like them?!
My body isn't tingling anymore...
Have I stopped mutating?
I was caught up
in my thoughts back then...
But the moment I noticed her...
...She was flying and bleeding...
...and looking at me,
like she'd seen a ghost!
I...
Hey, Luffy...
Which do you want over the other...
The human version of me,
totally unreliable and helpless...
...when faced with a female enemy?
Or the cruel, heartless warrior of science
able to beat up a monster like this...
Able to bring you the head of
anybody you want when ordered?
Which version of me
can help the Pirate King?
Without you, I...!
Dunno what's gonna happen, but...
That the Germa suit?!
I made up my mind.
It's probably all because I wore this...
...that the "science I've had
in my body since birth awakened.
Can't do a damn thing
about it now.
That's right! Accept it!
Show me Germa's science!
That said...
The "science" stops here!
Without you, I...!
I can't become the Pirate King!
I...
...refuse to be a Germa slave!
Man, right down the drain!
Show me your transformation!
Farewell, Germa!
Farewell...
Women's bath!
I'm gonna win this fight...
...no matter what happens after!
Ring, ring, ring...
Clik.
Have I had a Transponder Snail
on me the whole time?!
Who's calling me
at a time like this?!
Not now!
I snuck one into your waistband.
In case you found yourself
dying in a ditch or something.
Dumbass cook!
Quit buggin' me!
This won't take long, so listen.
We're gonna win against
the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Sure! That goes without sayin'!
But after the battle,
if I've lost my mind...
you gotta kill me.
Hey.
Yeah, I got you.
I'll make sure to kill you myself!
Dunno what your deal is,
but now I got something
to look forward to!
That said,
don't die until then!
Thanks.
Clik.
Where the hell'd you go?!
That more science of yours,
Son of Judge?!
Hey, now, you don't wanna
add fuel to the fire!
It's already blazing hot!
I'm gonna show you hell!
Hell Memories!